Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series VII is arranged in 151 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series VII. BY-LAWS, SYSTEM BOARDS OF ADJUSTMENT
  - Sub-Series 205-0. Bylaws
    - System Boards of Adjustment-General, 1930-1959 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Dec. 20, 1930-Nov. 24, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 205-1. Bylaws
    - 205-1(a). Atlantic Coast Line Board of Adjustment, 1950-1959 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Jan. 12, 1950-Sept. 17, 1959.
    - 205-1(a). Atlantic Coast Line Board of Adjustment, 1942-1949 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Mar. 17, 1942-Oct. 6, 1949.
    - 205-1(a). Atlantic Coast Line System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Aug. 26, 1921-Feb. 28, 1940.
    - 205-1(b). Atlantic Coast Line Board of Adjustment, 1939-1942 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-2. Bylaws
    - Illinois Central Board of Adjustment (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Illinois Central Board of Adjustment, 1921-1946 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-3. Bylaws
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1949 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-4. Bylaws
    - Delaware and Hudson Board of Adjustment, 1940-1959 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-8. Bylaws
    - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-9. Bylaws
    - Louisiana and Arkansas System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1952 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-12. Bylaws
    - Michigan Central Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-13. Bylaws
    - Central of Georgia System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1959 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-14. Bylaws
    - Louisville and Nashville Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Louisville and Nashville Board of Adjustment, 1926-1947 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Louisville and Nashville Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-15. Bylaws
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1942-1948 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1941 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-17. Bylaws.
    - 205-17-1. Allegheny District Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1921-1959 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - 205-17-2. Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, 1924-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 205-17-3. Trans-Missouri District Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 205-17-4. Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1920-1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 205-17-5. Kansas and Oklahoma-Midwest Department-Board of Adjustment, 1926-1959 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 205-17-6. South Atlantic District Board of Adjustment- Railway Express Agency, 1923-1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 205-17-7. Empire District Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1924-1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 205-17-8. Central Pacific Department Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 205-17-8. Central Pacific Department Board of Adjustment, 1921-1947 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 205-17-9. Northern District Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1924-1959 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 205-17-10. Gulf Department Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1922-1959 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 205-17-11. Ohio Valley and Eastern Lake District Board of Adjustment, 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 205-17-11. Ohio Valley and Eastern Lake District Board of Adjustment, 1923-1949 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 205-17-12. New England District Board of Adjustment- Railway Express Agency, 1928-1958 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 205-17-13. New York District Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1923-1959 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 205-17-14. South Pacific District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 205-17-15. Southwestern District Board of Adjustment, 1953-1960 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 205-17-15. Southwestern District Board of Adjustment, 1924-1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 205-17-16. North Pacific Board of Adjustment-Railway Express Agency, 1921-1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-18. Bylaws
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines Board of Adjustment, 1945-1959 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines Board of Adjustment, 1940-1944 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Southern Pacific-Pacific Lines Board of Adjustment, 1922-1939 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-19. Bylaws
    - Union Pacific-Lines East-Board of Adjustment (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Union Pacific-Western Lines-Board of Adjustment, 1934-1959 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-20. Bylaws
    - Pennsylvania System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1957 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 205-21. Bylaws
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - King Street Station Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-22. Bylaws
    - Northern Pacific Board of Adjustment, 1946-1959 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1945 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-23. Bylaws
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1958 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-21. Bylaws
    - 500 Line Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-25. Bylaws
    - M.K. and T. Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-26. Bylaws
    - N.C. and St. L. System Board of Adjustment (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-27. Bylaws
    - St. L.S.W. Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - St. L.S.W. Board of Adjustment, 1921-1947 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - St. L.S.W. Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-28. Bylaws
    - C. & O. System Board, 1921-1963 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-29. Bylaws
    - Western Pacific Board of Adjustment, 1929-1959 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 205-30. Bylaws
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1959 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Reading System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1946 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 205-31. Bylaws
    - B. & O. System Board of Adjustment, 1949-1959 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - B. & O. System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1948 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - B. & O. System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1943 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-32. Bylaws
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1932 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-34. Bylaws
    - Pere Marquette Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-35. Bylaws
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1959 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-36. Bylaws
    - Kansas City Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1941-1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-37. Bylaws
    - Union Depot Company, Columbus, Ohio, System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-47. Bylaws
    - C. St. P.M. & O. Board of Adjustment, 1936-1950 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-38. Bylaws
    - New York Central-Lines East-Board of Adjustment, 1952-1958 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - New York Central-Lines East-Board of Adjustment, 1923-1951 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - New York Central-Lines West-Board of Adjustment (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-40. Bylaws
    - Southern Pacific-Texas and Louisiana Lines-Board of Adjustment, 1921-1939 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-41. Bylaws
    - Boston and Albany System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-43. Bylaws
    - Spokane, Portland, and Seattle Board of Adjustment, 1924-1959 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-48. Bylaws
    - Norfolk Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-50. Bylaws
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1937 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-51. Bylaws
    - Toledo Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1951-1956 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-53. Bylaws
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1959 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-54. Bylaws
    - C. M. St. P. and P.-Lines East System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1959 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - C. M. St. P. and P.-Lines East System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1950 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - C. M. St. P. and P.,-Lines East System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-57. Bylaws
    - C. & N.W. System Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - C. & N.W. System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1947 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - C. & N.W. System Board, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-59. Bylaws
    - Washington Terminal Company Board of Adjustment, 1940-1954 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-60. Bylaws
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville System Board of Adjustment (Monon), 1926-1959 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 205-61. Bylaws
    - B.L.E. System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-62. Bylaws
    - Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1959 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 205-64. Bylaws
    - D.S.S. & A. System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1945 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 205-65. Bylaws
    - Belt Railway Company of Chicago System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1959 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 205-66. Bylaws
    - P. & L.E. Board of Adjustment, 1947-1959 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 205-67. Bylaws
    - C.B. & Q. Board of Adjustment, 1948-1959 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - C.B. & Q. Board of Adjustment, 1922-1940 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - C.B. & Q. System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-69. Bylaws
    - Southern Railway Board of Adjustment, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Southern Railway Board of Adjustment (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-70. Bylaws
    - C.P. & St. L. System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-76. Bylaws
    - Chicago Great Western Board of Adjustment, 1926-1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-78. Bylaws
    - Chicago and Southern Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-74. Bylaws
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific (C. R.I. & P.) System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-79. Bylaws
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1937-1959 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-81. Bylaws
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1959 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1920-1948 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-82. Bylaws
    - Florida East Coast System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1959 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 205-84. Bylaws
    - Missouri Pacific Board of Adjustment, 1946-1959 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Missouri Pacific Board of Adjustment, 1921-1945 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-85. Bylaws
    - Ann Arbor System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 205-86. Bylaws
    - Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-89. Bylaws
    - Los Angeles and Salt Lake Railroad (L. A. & St. L.) System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 205-90. Bylaws
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau Board of Adjustment, 1946-1959 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 205-97. Bylaws
    - Norfolk and Western Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 205-98. Bylaws
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois (C. E. & I.) System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1941 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 205-91. Bylaws
    - Western Maryland Board of Adjustment, 1946-1959 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-93. Bylaws
    - Camas Prairie Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-96. Bylaws
    - Rutland Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1958 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-99. Bylaws
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-100. Bylaws
    - Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-101. Bylaws
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Jan. 9, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 205-102. Bylaws
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Board of Adjustment, 1939-1959 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-103. Bylaws
    - Long Island System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1959 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-104. Bylaws
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1957 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-108. Bylaws
    - Chicago and Western Indiana System Board of Adjustment, 1944-1959 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-110. Bylaws
    - Midland Valley Board of Adjustment, 1936-1959 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 205-111. Bylaws
    - Maine Central System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1931 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-112. Bylaws
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis (C.C.C. & St. L.) Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-113. Bylaws
    - New York, Chicago, and St. Louis (N.Y. C. & St. L.) "Nickel Plate" System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1959 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 205-115. Bylaws
    - Oregon Short Line System Board of Adjustment, 1923-1925 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-116. Bylaws
    - Oregon-Washington Railroad and Navigation (O. W. R. & N.) System Board of Adjustment, 1922-1923 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 205-117. Bylaws
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 205-118. Bylaws
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford (N.Y. N.H. & H.) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1956 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 205-119. Bylaws
    - Central Vermont Railway Board of Adjustment, 1929-1957 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 205-120. Bylaws
    - Gulf Coast Lines Board of Adjustment, 1927-1959 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 205-121. Bylaws
    - Southeastern Express District Board of Adjustment, 1921-1937 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 205-122. Bylaws
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Board of Adjustment, 1943-1959 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 205-123. Bylaws
    - Grand Trunk Western Lines Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 205-126. Bylaws
    - Gulf & Ship Island, New Orleans & Great Northern, Alabama & Vicksburg, Vicksburg Shreveport & Pacific (G.&S.I.-N.O.G.N.-A. & V.-V.S.&P.) Mississippi Central System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 205-127. Bylaws
    - Denver & Rio Grande Western Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Denver & Rio Grande Western Board of Adjustment, 1921-1951 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-132. Bylaws
    - Seaboard Air Line Board of Adjustment, 1923-1959 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-135. Bylaws
    - New York, Ontario & Western (N. Y. O. & W.) System Board of Adjustment, 1931-1941 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-140. Bylaws
    - Virginian Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1941-1944 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-141. Bylaws
    - Arizona Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-152. Bylaws
    - Central Inspection & Weighing Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 205-153. Bylaws
    - Alabama & Vicksburg and Vicksburg, Shreveport and Pacific (A. V. & V. S. P.) System Board of Adjustment, 1922 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-154. Bylaws
    - Duluth, Missabe & Iron Range (D. M. & I.R.) System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1959 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-157. Bylaws
    - Wabash Board of Adjustment, 1922-1959 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-171. Bylaws
    - Pittsburgh & West Virginia System Board of Adjustment, 1947-1959 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-178. Bylaws
    - Canadian Pacific Railway (Lines East) System Board of Adjustment, 1924-1958 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Canadian Pacific (Prairie & Pacific Regions) Board of Adjustment, 1923-1959 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-180. Bylaws
    - Columbus & Greenville Board of Adjustment, 1943-1956 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-183. Bylaws
    - Canadian National Railway System Board of Adjustment-Lines East, 1921-1954 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - 205-183(b). Canadian National System Board-Lines East. Appeal, W.J. Evans, 1939-1943 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-187. Bylaws
    - Ogden Union Railway & Depot Company Board of Adjustment, 1923-1959 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 205-188. Bylaws
    - Chicago Union Station Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1941-1959 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 205-191. Bylaws
    - Boston Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      1955 July 12
  - Sub-Series 205-192. Bylaws
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1927-1959 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 205-195. Bylaws
    - City Bus Company Board of Adjustment, 1936-1959 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 205-198. Bylaws
    - Detroit & Toledo Shore Line Board of Adjustment, 1944-1946 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 205-211. Bylaws
    - St. Joseph Union Depot System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1942 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 205-215. Bylaws
    - New Orleans Public Belt Board of Adjustment, 1941-1959 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 205-216. Bylaws
    - Illinois Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1934-1959 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 205-220. Bylaws
    - Chicago South Shore and South Bend (C.S.S. & S. B.) System Board of Adjustment, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 205-221. Bylaws
    - Pacific Electric System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1959 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 205-230. Bylaws
    - Akron, Canton & Youngstown Board of Adjustment, 1939-1953 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 205-233. Bylaws
    - Clinchfield Board of Adjustment, 1947-1958 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 205-236. Bylaws
    - Canadian National Railway Express Division, 1935-1951 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 205-241. Bylaws
    - Canadian National Railways (Newfoundland Division), 1935-1959 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 205-251. Bylaws
    - Atlanta, Birmingham & Coast (A. B. & C.) System Board of Adjustment, 1921-1946 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 205-259. Bylaws
    - Chicago & Illinois Midland Board of Adjustment, 1942-1959 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 205-261. Bylaws
    - Litchfield & Madison Board of Adjustment, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 205-267. Bylaws
    - Ontario Northland Railway (formerly Temiskaming & Northern Ontario Railway), 1951-1958 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 205-268. Bylaws
    - Elgin, Joliet & Eastern System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1959 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 205-269. Bylaws
    - Tennessee Central System Board of Adjustment, 1951-1959 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 205-286. Bylaws
    - Fruit and Produce Handlers Board of Adjustment, 1943-1956 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 205-304. Bylaws
    - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Aug. 20, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 205-310. Bylaws
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency and Fruit Growers Express Boards of Adjustment, 1942-1959 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 205-322. Bylaws
    - Western Warehousing Company Board of Adjustment, 1942-1956 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 205-326. Bylaws
    - New York, Susquehanna and Western (N. Y. S. & W.) Board of Adjustment, 1944-1959 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 205-329. Bylaws
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Board of Adjustment, 1951-1953 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 205-332. Bylaws
    - Grain Elevator Employees of Canada System Board of Adjustment, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 205-333. Bylaws
    - Georgia Railroad. West Point Route Board of Adjustment, 1921-1959 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 205-413. Bylaws
    - Trailways Bus Depot, St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 205-416. Bylaws
    - Pan American Airways Board of Adjustment, 1946-1960 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 205-420. Bylaws
    - Northeast Airlines Inc. Board of Adjustment, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 205-425. Bylaws
    - Niagara, St. Catharines & Toronto System Board of Adjustment, 1945-1953 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 205-427. Bylaws
    - Freight Forwarding System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1959 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 205-428. Bylaws
    - Canadian Interior Navigation & Stevedoring Companies System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1959 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 205-432. Bylaws
    - Trans-Atlantic Shipping Companies System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1943 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 205-437. Bylaws
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. Board of Adjustment, 1946-1959 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 205-438. Bylaws
    - Capital (Pennsylvania-Central) Airlines Board of Adjustment, 1947-1959 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 205-465. Bylaws
    - The Pullman Company Board of Adjustment, 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 205-488. Bylaws
    - Western Air Lines Board of Adjustment, 1949-1959 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 205-490. Bylaws
    - Mid-Continent Airlines Board of Adjustment, 1947-1952 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 205-496. Bylaws
    - Toronto, Hamilton & Buffalo System Board of Adjustment, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 205-499. Bylaws
    - Bamberger Railroad Board of Adjustment, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      Jan. 10, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 205-517. Bylaws
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1948-1959 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 235-557. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 557-Mobile Lodge, Mobile, Alabama, 1922-1956 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      1922-Dec. 31, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 205-605. Bylaws
    - Canadian Pacific Express System Board of Adjustment, 1953-1959 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 205-675. Bylaws
    - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal Provisional Board of Adjustment, 1955-1959 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 205-678. Bylaws
    - Chicago Greyhound Terminal Inc. Board of Adjustment, 1955-1956 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 205-680. Bylaws
    - Algoma Central & Hudson Bay Railway Company, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 32)